Contact us for any inquiries: turkision@gmail.com
While Yakup Bey is the protector
and the owner of these lands..
no Turk will be a prisoner
or stay prisoners!
Cerkutay my valiant.
You should know
Yakup Bey values you.
Feed the valiant!
He has fallen weak!
Did you defeat us in battle
to ask us to kiss your hand?
If you ask me to walk with you...
...we will walk with you!
But if you want to take us
under your command...
...that's where you should stop!
My intention is good, Osman Bey
I am putting myself on the line for our union.
But you are lost in your pride
and rebel mei
You know what happens to those who rebel!
No I would never rebel!
Yakup Bey I know about your greatness.
Thank you
You did not leave us at the mercy of them
Thank you.
You helped us
Good
At least your pride is not an obstacle
for you to see the truth.
This is not pride!
But if you...
..want us to make a promise for a path...
....with no return...
..then it's impossible for me to
answer it without thinking first.
Everyone has made their decision without hesitation.
Except you.
If you are saying that you won't stand by my side...
...but against me.
...then that's something else.
Don't force me to do that!
Who are you to take me!?
No one can
take you from me!
Don't be afraid.
It's not me who should be afraid
It's youi
No one can touch her.
without killing me.
If that's your goal
come for me
I'll keep the Hatun
But she's not mine.
e don't own anything Orhan Bey.
We are all slaves to Germiyanid Yakup Bey.
We...
...are not slaves to anyone.
Your father Osman Bey will decide on that!
And he'll pay his respects
like all other Beys.
You want to attack to protect her
Your eyes are on fire.
You see the fire.
So stand back
Don't make me do it Mehmet Bey.
Do you love this Hatun?
Huh?
Will you marry her?
I can tell
I can tell you love the Hatun.
Then
I won't get in your way
I'll give you back your Hatun.
That's how my father taught me Orhan Bey
We'll protect each other in hard times.
Remember my favor to you.
Thank you.
Thank you Mehmet Bey.
We...
...never forget what's done to us.
But we know.
...that it's a weak man's job...
...to take advantage of a favor.
It's a weak man's job
not to return the favor, Orhan
Don't get crushed under our favor.
Those who know they're great shouldn't worry.
If you dare to go against me again.
I'll crush you.
Here.
Ayran
Drink and cool down
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
No
This fire...
...comes from anger
Only one thing can cool it.
And that's blood.
Untie the Hatun
That was for tying me to the tree.
Orhan.
She's trouble Orhan.
You won't get away with it.
You wannabe Bey!
Come on.
The Flagless!
I brought you my Germiyanid father Yakup Bey's regards,
who will rule over great lands,
Yakup Bey asks for your promise
With the coin we gave for the hatun
I have no doubts you'll make the right decision.
Stay safe
Karesi Bey
what about you?
Are you not with me?
take the bull by the horns Yakup Bey
Of course I do
And now.
you should do what's needed Osman Bey
As you heard.
...everyone is with me.
I don't make my
decision with quantity
Hi it
about something I don't know much about
I don't make rushed decisions
When everyone has a side
those who don't take one.
.. will be wiped off the board.
Those who are afraid to be wiped off the board...
would never be able to do what I do.
Now tell me Yakup Bey...
Tell me.
Was it just you who came here to save me?
MashAllah
MashAllah to the beys
You came all this way
Thank you
Thank you. Thank you.
We haven t seen you in a long time too.
You all came to our lands
Thank you
Thank you Osman Bey.
Since you're here...
...then I want to host you in
Yenisehir tomorrow.
I want to prepare a nice meal for you all.
I've been desiring to visit Yenisehir
for a while now Osman Bey.
We'll come.
Thank you thank you.
Osman Bey
We want to hear your loyalty
..and you talk about a meal
One who sees with their eyes...
would choose the good tent.
I wanted to..
visit the beyhoods under my rule..
one by one.
...and see their order.
If you're inviting us...
then let us start the inspection...
...with Yenisehir, then.
Our system is organized.
and our city is rich.
Yakup Bey
I want to host you at my table too.
Where is Cerkutay?
He's free
He chooses where he goes
Stay safe
He's trying to
buy time by inviting us for a meal
He must be planning on a deception
Won't we go my bey?
We will go
He can make all the games he wants.
I'm the one who wrote down the plan he's making
Send men everywhere
Let everyone know
how Osman lost his reputation.
As you wish my bey
While Turks make each other suffer..
we will take back
Rome's land back from them
And of course our revenge.
You successfully completed the first part of your mission
Well done, Remus.
I m ready to do
everything for Christianity.
We're going to start a fire Remus.
We're going to start a fire of rebellion in their own cities...
and I intend to start it in Sogut.
Master Vasilis!
I've got news from our men in Konya
It's about the treasure then
Osman’s son, Alaeddm
They say that he was the last person to see the Sultan
Alaeddin
He must have left that place with his hands full.
Remus!
Osman must be looking for you everywhere
You know what you need to do.
I do Master Vasilis.
Go on
The light of Christ is with us.
We're going to revive Rome!
Cerkutay..
I can't even find joy in the fact that.
Cerkutay is free now
He both took my valiant away from me..
and put chains around our necks.
He only wants to destroy our reputation
and he succeeded.
Germiyanids are good men, my Bey.
You're wrong He wouldn t have lined
up all the Beys behind him.
if his intention was good
He wouldn't have wanted me to kiss
his hand light after he saved us Bayindir
The Beys will surely not side with us anymore
Remus must be serving Yakup Bey then my Bey.
This is just a race to see who gets to the top
He has no problem working with traitors
or heathens in the meantime
They even went after Sultan Mesud
How are we supposed to know
if Yakup Bey is a part of this or not?
What do you want us to do my Bey"?
The meal we're going to prepare
is going to buy us some time
You will find Remus and bring
him to me while we do so.
As you command my Bey.
We will then see who are traitors and who are not.
Let's go
The dream of a state is a legacy from our ancestors!
We’re not going to let tricksters take it away now
Get back to your jobs!
Come on!
What's wrong?
Poor man Seems like
he's been through a lot
I know him! That's Cerkutay!
He's one of Osman Bey's Alps
We thought he was a martyr.
That's Cerkutay!
-What happened'?
Osman Bey was captured by the Lord.
Yakup Bey, son of Germiyan rescued him.
Osman Beys reputation is destroyed then
Shame on those who's putting us through this.
This road won't take us to Kestel
We're going to
Yenisehir, not Kestel
Yenisehirt? Then we part ways here.
Andre! We are going to Kestel!
You are not going anywhere!
I told you to let go of me!
The path is not safe.
We will go to Yenisehir first
And we will decide what to do there!
Such a pityi What happened to youi?
Who are you?
Where is the Orhan I left!?
Your anger is putting a veil between us Holofira
I am the same Orhan
And you are the same Holofira.
Lord's daughter Holofira...
who took shelter in oui tribe
But there is a difference
What's that?
You know how to use a sword now,
Lord's daughter.
If you don't get out of my way
I will give you a bigger wound Orhan the bandit!
I have no doubt.
You can do that
Enough Orhan!
Why are you laughing। You tried to trade me for gold!
They gifted me like a slave!
Because of who? Because of you!
You were the one to harm me the most!
- And now you are...
-I promise you!
I will make them pay for all of this!
All of this
Make them pay!?
I don't need anyone's help.
Let go of me.
Let go!
Watch out! I am Cerkutay!
I will cut you down with
my dual swords! Open the gates!
He is here! Inform Malhun Hatun!
Cerkutay Bey came back!
Cerkutay Bey?
Cerkutay?
Cerkutay!
This is not a dream right?
You are really here!
Ul...
Thank Allah
You are alive.
Mother?
Is this man my
Yes sweetie
I told you your father would come.
He's here now.
Your father's here Cerkutay
You're my father Cerkutay.
Father!
Ulgen
Your patience is rewarded thank Allah
Now that I saw they're together..
I couldnt be happier.
Thank you my Great Allah
You gave my father back to me.
Come father
Come.
Come on. Come on.
Come on father.
Come on father
Welcome to your home.
Cerkutay Bey
Come on father.
We've been waiting for you Cerkutay Bey Where were you
My mother and I waited for long.
But you never showed
Hold on son.
He talks a lot
I wondei who he takes after.
They all say I take after you
Because you talk a lot
He never speaks
Mother why doesn't Cerkutay Bey ever speak?
I've waited so long
They looked for you
Osman Bey nevei stopped looking
Osman Bey
would find me if he looked enough.
I'll get your bath ready.
Okay?
You can take off your clothes Cerkutay.
No
They
They will all see me like this
They're waiting for the old Cerkutay
They can wait.
Bey Father
Bey Father I have good news.
Fatma"?
Fatma what is it?
Cerkutay
Cerkutay Bey is back.
So he's back you say
Malhun'?
Come on Fatma
Call my valiant.
He's in his room my by we wanted to let him rest
You say so.
Okay then.
Let him rest.
Let him rest a bit more.
Let him
My Osman...
...you're smiling but...
...something else
is going on with you.
Why did Cerkutay return alone?
They gave good news but.
...they ruined our reputation.
Remus
Remus tricked us
How did that happen?
Malhun.
We'll talk about this later
Boran
My Bey!
Prepare a good big home for Cerkutay
Yes my bey.
Malhun
Piepare a big dinner.
I've started the preparations my bey.
The table will be set by the time they're here.
Good
They've checked all the inns and caves until the surrounding area of Egrimese.
But they couldn't find that lowlife Remus.
Send word to the spies.
to check all the inn that
non Muslim tradesmen frequent one by one
Remus is no ordinary tradesmen.
He won t let where he's staying be known easily
That's why we should be
offering a prize to those who knows where he is.
Veysel
My beys!
What's up, beardless Veysel?
Where are you coming from?
I got horseshoes made in Bilecik
I took them and I'm going to Yenisehir Bayindir Bey
When I was coming back I saw that tiadesmen Remus
I called to him but he didn't hear.
How is Cerkutay?
Did you manage to save him?
Remus'?
Where did you see that lowlife, tell me Veysel.
It was near Karakiyi my bey.
He was going while constantly checking his back
Then again there's not a lot where he's going.
At most it would be..
He's going to the hunting grounds of Flagless.
Come on
Go on then
Go and find Remus
GERMIYANIDS BORDER
How can Osman not swear loyalty to you
when he owes you his life and freedom, father?
There's nothing else to do now
Enough Mehmet Enough
When Gonca comes with Sultan's firman from Konya
..Osman Bey...
will swore his loyalty.
There's no killing
Theie's no drawing swords.
These are the last resorts.
The wisdom of politics Mehmet.
The wisdom of politics
Attention
The great Germiyanid's
Bey, Yakup Bey's...
...magnificent hatun: Saadet Hatun!
May Allah bless you Saadet Hatun
May Allah bless you!
We re setting up the bazaar at the skirts.
Osman...
...won't be able to act freely
like he used to.
He won't be able to...
He won't, father, but...
...what about the arrow shot at you?
Won't we make them pay for that?
Shut up, your mother will hear.
What are you saying Mehmet?
Saadet Hatun
Who?
Who shot you with that arrow my bey?
It's nothing hatun
They can't take me down that easily.
You’re supporting me
Osman, Osman
He ambushed father and pointed his arrow at him!
Yakup Beyl
You never spare the lives of those who attack you!
Why is Osman still alive?
Why did you spare his life?
I didn't spare anyone's life Hatun
Then
you must be waiting for the right time.
A Hatun knows her husband
Too much blood will be spilled if I kill him.
Before he pledges his allegiance to me
He'll first obey...
...and then he'll answer for what he did.
Oh, and...
I did punish Osman for his impertinence.
I destroyed his reputation.
All the people
talk about how
Osman was humiliated
May I come in my Bey?
Come.
My Beyl
Remus tricked Osman and then vanished
as you commanded him to.
No one knows where he is.
Osman must be after Remus by now
Make sure Remus stops breathing before they get to him
As you command, my Bey
Osman Bey invited us to Yenisehir
Mehmet!
You'll be in charge of preparations.
Listen carefully now.
Caravansarai.
Watch your backs
We will not be alone on our way to Yenisehir.
We've taken precautions,
my Shahzade(Prince).
Good.
You know what to do, Gonca
Go now.
So we meet again, Gonca Hatun
Is this merely a coincidence
or are you following us?
My father Yakup Bey is at the border market
near Yenisehir, Alaeddin Bey.
They say that you know about everything
Didn't you know about this?
You know a lot about me, Gonca Hatun...
...and since we're both going to be
on the same road, you should be our guests.
Come join us.
We're the owner of these lands, not guests.
Innkeeper!
Prepare those tables for us.
-Innkeeper!
-My Bey
Bring us that famous soup of yours.
As you command
You're going to do as I say
if you don't want my men...
...to destroy this Caravansarai...
Listen carefully!
We deserve that map.
I'm not going to let you have that treasuie,
Madrasah Student
Just go on and enjoy your meal
Innkeeper!
Be carefull
Where is the soup'?
Coming my Bey!
Come on!
Take it
Bring it.
Eat, madrasah student!
May I come in my Bey?
Come in.
Cerkutay
My valiant!
My valiant soldier.
Come here
Your clothes will get dirty.
What are you talking about?
Forget it now!
Come here.
My Cerkutay...
Look at me.
Look.
Are you better?
Cerkutay?
You're okay!
You're okay! Huh?
Good good Right?
Let me kiss your hand my bey.
Praise be.
uome on
You must be hungry.
Ulgen!
Malhun!
Malhun bring the food!
The food's here my
Bey! Come on, sisters.
Let's eat.
Let's eat now
Come on
Here are your favorite dishes, Cerkutay!
Come here and sit down.
Cerkutay
My valiant, the seat of honor is yours.
Seat of honor?
Seat of honor is mine???
You must have missed this.
You must be hungry
Come on, start.
In the name of Allah
the merciful the beneficent...
Boran
what about Cerkutay's house?
I prepared it
with the help of Allah, my Bey
I prepaied the biggest and...
...fanciest house in Yenisehir
for my brother.
It has a garden too.
A garden?
You can make me a swing there,
right Cerkutay?
Are you kidding me?
Don't be like this Cerkutay!
After all those years of imprisonment!
What house could heal my wounds?
Of course not.
We just thought it would ease your pain.
You can spend nice days
with your family there, Cerkutay
What about the things I lost?
Who will bring them back, Osman Bey?
Do you know why I came back
looking like this?
So you could see what I've gone through!
You gave me food and bread, thank you!
But
They took my arm
I can't even hold a bread!
Don't worry.
We will make them pay for all of that!
Will you?
Or are you going to leave
that to Yakup Bey, too?
Welcome to our palace, Lord's daughter.
Yeah right.
I will never forget that you
brought me here like a slave!
I know your memory is strong.
You never forget.
Come on.
Cerkutay.
I waited!
I waited for my Bey and my brothers to come!
You didn't!
None of you did!
Cerkutay...
We looked for you.
Don't say that.
I'd never leave you!
We looked everywhere.
If Osman Bey looked for me.
He'd find me even if
I was buried under ground.
You left me at the hands
of the infidels, my Bey!
Cerkutay...
My valiant...
Look at me!
Look at me.
I know you the best.
I understand you.
You don't know anything.
I was a valiant.
I was an Alp!
I fought until...
...the last drop of my blood.
I fell captive.
I lived with rats and dogs!
They tortured my whole body.
I didn't give up.
I never backed down on my duty.
I didn’t speak one word.
Cerkutay.
I completed my duty Osman Bey.
I did what a good Alp would!
Did you do what a Bey would, Osman Bey?
What did you do Osman Bey?
Everyone's talking about us out there.
They're disrespecting us.
Cerkutay.
Do you know
why they're disrespecting us?
For whom?
For whom, my valiant?
Do you know why we were trapped?
I don't know about you.
But I..
...fell for your cause.
Cerkutay.
Come on! Go now.
Go and get some rest.
Go.
It's too painful to hear it, eh?
I lived that.
You can't even stand to hear it.
Come on Cerkutay.
Leave.
Leave Cerkutay.
I'm sorry, my Bey
He is not...
Osman Bey...
He'll calm down in time.
My Bey!
Boran.
Go with him.
Don't leave him alone.
Sure my Bey.
I am joyless, can't eat.
My Bey
Holofira?
A place with a huge garden!
What a shame!
You couldn't fit in that huge palace!
But you fit my whole family
in this room huh!?
All that time.
Nights bled into days...
...days bled into nights.
Don't do this.
Don't do what Ulgen?
Don't do what?
What about you?
I left you in our home
Why did you come here?
I...
Osman Bey didn't want us to stay there
all by ourselves while you're gone.
We came here to stay until you come back.
I'm back.
I'm back. I'm back.
Go gather your stuff
We're leaving.
Sister Ulgen
You take my niece and leave
Let me fulfill my longing with my brother.
Osman Bey is very mad about this.
Your son looted my caravan
with bunch of looters!
They tried to sell me off like a slave!
Orhan Bey must have an excuse
for what you've gone through.
Don't worry Holofira.
We will cover your losses.
I dont want gold from you, Malhun Hatun.
I want to go back home.
I understand you Holofira.
But don’t raise your voice.
Don't forget who you're talking to.
You can go back home
whenever you want
Isn't that right Orhan Bey?
Holofira
You can't go now
-Firstly...
...you need to rest Holofira.
You look very tired.
They will accompany you to your room
Am I a hostage...
or a guest who can leave
whenever she wants?
You're our guest girl
We dont keep our hostages
in our palace...
...but in our dungeon.
How can you make my mother talk
with that disrespectful girl, brother?
Fatma!
Watch the words...
coming out of your mouth.
Orhan!
Mother!
Don't...
...don't even think about
sending Holafira.
Are you still talking about her?
What are you going to do with
a woman who doesn't even want you?
She has clearly moved on!
Stop it!
Tell me, Orhan Bey...
...did you complete youi mission?
May I come in Malhun Haton?
Come in!
Osman Bey wants to see Orhan Bey.
The brother I had...
...wouldn't have left me behind!
How could you leave me behind Boran Bey?
Don't say that brother!
We searched everywhere we could for you!
I...
I Cerkutay...
I endured tortures
for all these years by myself!
I was given no food!
or water!
I even lost my arm!
But I didn't sell you out!
I didn't speak a single word!
A single word!
Not even a single word!
Neither about Osman Bey..
nor about the people
I thought were my brothers!
I didn’t sell you out.
Brother
It wasn't the enemy that broke me...
...it was the fact that
I had no one, Boran!
Don't say anything else now.
What did you do about the flagless, Orhan?
Earning their trust...
...seemed difficult my Bey.
Did you expect it to be easy, Orhan?
I attacked a Caravan with them..
...to show them my skills
and earn their favor.
I'm asking you if the job is done or not.
I'm not asking you about anything else
It's not done yet, my Bey.
...but it will be.
Why are you here then, Orhan?
How are you going to persuade the Flagless?
I will show them that
as long as they're flagless(without country)...
no treasure will give
them comfort, my Bey.
That's going to be my move.
I would have done it by now, but...
...Something I didn't expect-
The Hatun you didn't expect to be there
is now here in the palace.
The Caravan I attacked with the Flagless...
..turned out to be Holafira's caravan,
my Bey.
I couldn't leave her there father.
So you became hope
for someone who needed it.
But even though you did that...
...that still doesn't mean
you can just fail your mission.
Wait for me in the yard tomorrow morning.
As you command my Bey.
Caravansarai
They must be asleep now. Come on Huseyin.
Don't forget what I told you.
As you command Gonca Hatun.
What's this map for, my Sultan?
The map of Seljuk treasure.
You...
Who are you?
-Alps!
-Catch him!
Alps!
Wake up!
Who are you?
Close all the exits!
No one will leave!
My shahzade(Prince)!
Baysungur!
Search all the rooms, come on!
Alps! Come on!
Until we find where that dog hides
we will knock every door!
Watch it Alaeddin Bey!
This is Gonca Hatun's room!
She is sleeping!
Then call her and wake her up!
No one will sleep until I find
the dog that entered my room!
Alaeddin Bey why are you shouting
in front of my door!?
I want to search your room Gonca Hatun.
A bandit entered my room.
Were your alps out for a night stroll?
Whatever...
Come inside, there is no one in there.
Tell your alps to be
more careful Alaeddin Bey.
Well they don t teach you that
in the Madrasah, right?
Alps...
I don't want this to happen again.
As you command my shahzade(Prince).
Get back to your duties now.
Come on.
You are not as smart as me,
madrasah student!
Alaeddin!
You can't outsmart me, Hatun.
She says I am not a prisoner!
I'd be in a dungeon if I were a prisoner!
What's the difference?
Orhan.
This is all your fault.
Holofira.
You changed a lot.
But still...
...your eyes still look the same.
This Hatun is mine now.
No one touches her...
before going past me.
Don't be stupid Holofira!
Get it together!
Pull yourself together!
You didn't forget him...
...but he never looked for you.
He never came.
He's not the Orhan you're waiting for.
He's just a forager who raided your caravan.
Kismet!
I'm here, my Hatun.
Kismet.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
I haven't walked
outside in months.
I'm sick of it.
Let's go outside tomorrow.
I need to get some air.
But Bala Hatun...
You heard what I said Kismet.
Get ready.
As you wish.
I stopped but the enemy won't.
I've been fighting for a long time.
But I haven't seen a man who fights
as good as you my Bey.
Praising the enemy is a weapon.
The arrogance will cause mistakes.
You learned that well
But It doesn't work on me.
Slander and insult
It leads the enemy to doubt.
And doubt makes you make mistakes.
Just like the Flagless do.
They wanted to make you do
a raid with slander.
And the result?
The result is defeat.
It's hard times...
I don't want any mistakes Orhan.
As you wish my bey.
Take this.
Here my bey
Thank you
The name of Allah the merciful,
the compassionate.
My Bey...
Cerkutay...
Yes'?
I can't convince him my Bey.
He insists on leaving.
If he doesn't believe in us anymore...
...then let him.
May Allah wish his future be bright.
-Boran!
-My bey
Send word to the tribe.
The alps will be inspected!
Tomorrow will be tough!
As you wish my bey.
Cerkutay
Should you rethink maybe?
Where will we go?
I said we will leave Ulgen!
I can't stay another night at this palace!
This is our home!
Why are we leaving?
If you want it so much you leave
Cerkutay!
How can you say that to your father?
He s making us leave our home mother!
Why don't you get mad at him?
Do you not want to leave?
No! Everyone is here.
Osman Bey.
Uncle Boran!
Uncle Gurbuz!
Sister Fatma!
All of them are here.
What am I going to do without them?
What about me?
Did you not miss me?
I did miss you but...
I don't even know you.
This palace is not the place
for you to get to know me.
What does that mean?
Don't you want to become an Alp?
I do!
Let s go and get to know each other then.
I will teach you how to become an Alp.
No one can do it better than I do!
Cerkutay Alp!
Good then.
Let's go Cerkutay Bey.
GERMIYANIDS BORDER
If Osman Bey still refuses to obey...
...after Gonca is back from Konya, my Bey...
May I come in my Bey'?
Come in, son!
Are we all set?
We are, my Bey.
Ten thousand horsemen
are waiting at Cukuragzi.
They are waiting but...
...are we really going to attack Yenisehir?
The last thing I want...
...is to spill the blood of my own.
However....
Osman made the first move against us.
The meal he invited us to
might as well be an ambush.
Stay here then.
I will go destroy Osman.
Mehmet!
Son!
While all the Beys are going to be there
I have to show up especially after
I made my intention to be the Sultan.
Don't worry.
We're prepared for anything.
My Mehmet...
Thousands of Alps with you as their commander.
That's all the security we need son.
We're going to go there.
Sit around their table and
look them in their eyes.
If Osman makes a move on our lives...
Then you will then attack Yenisehir.
You will leave no human being alive!
I ignored about the arrow shot at you my Bey.
...but if they make
the slightest attempt on your life...
...no one can stop what will happen next.
Let's go.
So you're saying that those who set me and Orhan up
now trapped Alaeddin in Konya...
Right.
I can't wait for him to be back.
Don't worry.
Don't worry at all.
My son is clever.
Alaeddin will be fine even if they attack him.
Well...
it's not the enemy w
e're competing against
We're competing against our own.
This is just the beginning.
I want everything to be all set Malhun.
Make sure we have everything
we need tonight.
The sherbet and the food are ready, my Bey
...but it looks like you
mean something else.
Don't worry.
We will take measurements
in the palace, too.
When Konur brings Remus tonight...
...things will come to a conclusion.
You were just dried herbs.
...and when cooked the remedy
hidden within you came out.
If you ask whose remedy this is...
....the answer is the one
that looks for a remedy.
Bala Hatun.
Come have a seat at my table.
We can't refuse an invitation Dervish Efendi.
Thank you.
But how do you know my name?
It would be a shame if I didn't know
the name of the Sheikh Edebali's daughter.
Have a seat
You have a seat as well.
You brought some herbs to the lodge.
Thank you.
But I'm used to living with
this illness Dervish.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Getting used to is different...
...than being patient.
Like Hadrat Eyyub...
Bala Hatun.
Eyyub Hadrath
had many blessings for 80 years.
He had many kids
many possessions
but
a test for him came along.
One night..
while his family was sleeping...
Eyyub's home was demolished.
Ten of his kids...
...were under the wreck.
He suffered a lot.
But his test was not over.
One day he woke up and..
saw that he had boils all over him.
No doctor could find a cure.
Days went by...
...and Eyub Hadrath's body
was covered in scars
But he was like a mulberry leaf, Eyub Hadrath.
The same way the mulberry leaf remains calm
as it transforms into cloth.
...he too remained calm
and didn't complain.
It s said that eighteen years went by...
All the doctors were desperate...
...as none of the ointments worked.
His body was covered in nothing but scars.
His wife Rahime came to him one day
and said that "Oh Eyub...
...just pray so that Allah
saves you from your troubles"
Eyub looked at his wife and said that.
"How can I ask for such a thing?"
"He gave me 80 years filled with joy
of my children and prosperity"
"How can I complain now?"
"Let me suffer for another 80 years"
...and then I might consider that"
Eyyub Hadrath.
...was a prophet.
He had companions.
And this trouble benefited the devil.
He poisoned the hearts of his companions.
They started talking.
"What kind of prophet
can't find a remedy for himself?"
"Where is the miracle?"
They abandoned Eyyub one by one.
But Eyyub Hadrath did not complain.
Years passed his wounds
were festered with maggots
The maggots reached his hearts and tongue
Then Eyyub's heart was filled with fear.
"If the maggots eat my heart and tongue..
how can I pray?"
He prayed to Allah
and great Allah rewarded his patience.
...by healing his wounds.
He had more children than the ones he lost.
He was rewarded with more richness.
Like Hadrath Eyyub...
...those who wait patiently.
...good news come soon Bala Hatun.
I pray that...
...you will find your remedy
with these herbs.
Thank you dervish.
It's already giving me strength.
6 great Beys will sit on each table
The heart of the Turkmens will beat here!
They will all feel as if they are in
their own homeland, but..
...they will see that...
...the one who will unite these lands
is Osman Bey.
You will put the famous furs of Esrefoglus there.
Yes my Bey
You will put carpets of the Karesioglus there.
Yes my Bey.
Come here brother.
You know what you are going to do for
Germiyanid Yakup Bey.
We know my Bey.
Come on
Beys are about to arrive.
Brothers
if anything goes wrong,
you will all pay for that
As you command Boran Bey!
Come on.
Come on sisters!
You have guests?
Go to your room I will prepare
something to wear for you.
There is no need Fatma Hatun.
Who are the guests?
The Turkmen Beys in the border lands.
I will send your meal to your room
You don't want your guests to see me?
Well...
...how are you going
to introduce me right?
The loot your bandit brother got from the pillage?
Don't call my brother a bandit again!
-Or...
-Or?
What are you going to do?
Fatma!
Excuse her.
I'm not mad at her.
I'm mad at you.
When can I go home, Orhan?
I'll take you myself.
But have patience.
These are hard times.
How’s your wound?
Which one are you asking?
Either!
She's crazy
O Allah!
You can't go anywhere...
...before you speak.
Yavuz! You traitor!
Aykurt!
Tie this dog's hands.
As long as he lives...
...they won't stop.
He won't die until
we get what we want from Remus.
Come on!
We're going to Yenisehir.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you too.
Welcome.
We're glad you're here.
Thank you Osman Bey!
Thank you Osman bey
You prepared well.
You greeted us with kindness.
There are so many Beys here.
We did what's necessary Yakup Bey.
-Turahan
-My Bey?
Go on.
Come Yakup Bey.
Orhan.
My Bey.
You will wait for Remus
This will end tonight.
It will be a tough night, huh?
As you wish my bey.
Osman Bey
Here, here hatuns.
Welcome hatuns.
MashAllah, mashAllah.
You built a palace worthy of
your name Malhun Hatun
Until dinner please have a seat here.
Welcome Saadet Hatun.
Have a seat there.
Good work Malhun Hatun.
The palace turned out nice.
Thank you.
Hatuns..
Fitnat!
Prepare 100 rolls of our fabrics
for Malhun Hatun.
Once these walls are decorated
with those...
...then...
...it will really look like a palace.
Thank you Saadet Hatun.
But we don't need anything
more than this.
All the fabrics are have have been woven
by our great Kayi hatuns
You can give those fabrics to our hatuns.
Here Yakup Bey.
Here, Karesi Bey.
Candar Bey.
Here.
Felekuddin Bey, here please.
Mubanzeddin Bey here please.
Is this a new tradition Osman Bey?
Even our places have been decided beforehand.
It's quite good
From now on...
...everything has an order.
You made it look like our patterns, praise be!
You must know of it Osman Bey.
These lands...
were visited by many of our blood.
Some of them...
...didn't take our land as their own.
They thought of us as strangers.
The moves they made..
...disturbed our order.
So...
...that's why...
...we didn't want
you to feel strange.
Recognize our home...
...as your own...
...Recognize us as...
...one of your own, if Allah permits.
Yakup Bey.
Why is there no Germiyanid
mark on your spot'?
Allah Allah!
-Boran!
-My Bey!
How could you miss such a detail?
Forgive me, my Bey.
It's okay.
Such small mistakes can take place.
Kanyumaz!
Well, then.
Let's take our seats.
Don't worry my Beys.
Every piece of land I sit on
is Germiyanid land.
Your home...
..is my home.
Thank you.
That's what we wanted to tell you.
From now on all of our moves...
...will be based on that fact, if Allah permits.
- Boran!
- My Bey.
Bring the sherbet here.
As you command, my Bey
Go on.
I have news from Mehmet Bey.
The Alps have surrounded Yenisehir, my Bey
Here my Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
Enjoy it.
In the name of Allah
the merciful, the compassionate.
We heard that you're going to be staying
at the borders for some time Saadet Hatun.
What you heard is right.
There's much work to do
around the borders.
We will be around for some time.
We'll see each other more often then,
Saadet Hatun
Indeed.
Who is the pretty girl, Malhun Hatun?
Is she your daughter in law?
Daughter in law?
We didn't know.
Is she Orhan Bey's wife?
Holafira is our guest here.
Princess Holafira.
As Malhun Hatun said
I'm a guest here.
I thought that Malhun Hatun
had Orhan marry a foreigner'
You've got some funny jokes, don't you?
What brought you to these lands
princess Holofira?
Trade.
I came here to trade like you.
Get up.
How are the preparations?
The weapons are on the way, sir.
Our traders that earned their trust
hide the weapons among other goods.
We tolerated them for a reason all these years.
These bottles will explode
in the places they think the safest.
These swords will cut the people
they love the most.
Soldiers of Jesus Christ!
There wont be any soldier left
that does not hold a sword!
Your neighbors...
...your alp friends
the people you dined with...
...those who tried to assimilate us for years!
They will die by our hands!
They won't sleep anymore!
Because we are awake!
Tell me Tesehus.
What about the other locations'?
50 more joined us in Karacahisar.
And the Christians in Sogut
are ready to fight beside us.
Master Vasilis,
the fire of rebellion you lit...
...is growing each day.
It will grow...
It will giow bigger...
Everything will be ready before grand master arrives.
Are you ready to destroy the Turks!?
We are!
Jesus Christ is with us!
Gonca Hatun.
Is one of your alps is missing?
Your memory is strong, student.
Yes I don't forget what I read,
and what I see.
I sent a messenger to my Bey father.
Why are you so curious?
Do you think the bandit that entered
your room was one of us?
Why would you send an alp in my room?
There is nothing you can take from me.
Right?
If I had sent an alp
I would have taken what I wanted, student.
It looks like there was a plan.
There is someone close to me
that likes playing games...
Forget about games now!
Show me your skills.
Let's see if your mind is strong enoug
h to control your horse, too!
Come on!
You don't know me at all, Gonca Hatun.
He is just like his father.
We will follow them from a distance.
We will, tool Come on!
Come on!
May peace and mercy of Allah be upon you.
May peace and mercy of Allah be upon you
Mother!
Alaeddin Ali?
Son
Mother
Don't son You'll get sick Alaeddin
I can't take it mother.
I miss you so much.
I miss you!
Mother.
Mother!
Are you okay?
You're okay! Praise be!
If you're okay!
I'm okay.
You'll be okay, right mother?
Mother?
Sit down.
Drink it mother.
Mother.
Drink it.
Tell me son.
How are things in Konya?
Konya's the same mother.
But Yakup Bey
...will cause trouble.
He sent his daughter to Konya.
I know son.
I know.
He causes trouble here too.
What is it mother'?
Yakup Bey
...asked your father to obey.
My Shehzade(Prince).
Get the horses ready
This silence is no good.
Until Yakup Bey leaves Yenisehir...
..we'll stay cautious.
As you wish my Shehzade(Prince).
Where are your sons Osman Bey?
I can't see them
They have a duty.
Your sons are absent as well.
What happened?
They are out to get me good news,
if Allah permits.
If Allah permits, if Allah permits.
Well...
Let's get to the case.
What's the sultan issue you have?
It's not an issue.
It's the truth Osman Bey.
What is it?
Do you have something to say?
Of course.
The hereditary rights...
...belonged to Sultan Mesut before he died.
It's clear...
And the Beys know that.
...you...
...haven't even paid Konya taxes for years.
Well...
Do you want to be the heir to Seljuk State...
...that you were never loyal to?
Victory comes from courage...
...not loyalty Osman Bey.
Maybe...
...Sultan Mesut and I...
...didn't get along...
...but..
...I walked a very straight path.
Beys know that as well.
You're right Yakup Bey.
You're right.
And...
...you lead the way to us too.
You say...
...that if you want to lead...
...you'll have to fight the leader!
You speak of courage!
Not loyalty.
Osman Bey.
I earned my freedom...
...with my own grace.
And you...
...took it from Sultan Mesut's hands.
Also...
Don't forget this:
Neither...
...am I Konya
who has surrendered to Mongols
...nor you are me.
Don't think I'm advising you something.
Every Bey here...
..in this invitation...
...have no choice but to follow my lead...
What if the path you're walking is wrong?
I saved you from
imprisonment, Osman Bey.
It's clear who's on the right path.
I'm not saying with bad intent.
During my rule as the Sultan...
...I don't wish for situations like this.
We're not afraid of shahada...
...we are not afraid of
imprisonment either!
Can I come in my bey?
Come in Boran
My bey
We have Remus.
With your permission beys.
You have the permission Osman Bey.
Go and come back swiftly.
We still have things to talk about.
Has it been decided when
the border market will open Saadet Hatun?
It will open in two days Hatice Hatun.
Haven't your caravans made it yet?
Sevilay Hatun?
They will be at the
border market tomorrow morning.
Can anyone...
...enter this border market?
Of course.
We will make agreements with the Lords
near the borders.
Caravans from India and
Constantinople will come.
Princess Holofira.
You said you were interested in trade.
We invite you too.
Holofira is here for a short time
We have high hopes
for the border market, Hatuns.
The better the goods...
...the greater our name will be.
Your stall is ready too, Malhun Hatun
Thank you Saadet Hatun.
You must've heard about
Yenisehir's name for trading.
I haven't.
Then your name hasn't made it
to Germiyan lands.
Speaking of which...
...what can Kayi do apart from rugs?
Then you'll see it yourself
at the market, Saadet Hatun.
Speak!
Tell me.
So you...
...were playing games behind my Bey huh?
Do you remember what I told you?
I told you that if you did
something behind my back.
I'd make you pay.
Do you remember?
It seems that you don't.
But you will now.
Come here!
Look at me!
Come here.
Give me that.
Look at me!
Didn't I tell you that I'd rip your tongue off?
Didn't I tell you that I'd carve your eyes out?
You're going to talk.
You are going to talk!
I can't
They'd kill me.
I'm the one that will kill you.
Not anyone else. Talk!
Yakup Beyl
Yakup Bey set it all up!
He did it to...
...destroy your reputation.
...If you're lying again...
The letter! It's in my pocket!
Check it out.
My Bey.
-Kanyumaz
-Stay still
Yakup's man Kanyumaz..
He gave me the letter.
Look at me
If this is a lie...
...It's the truth for Christ's sake!
Yakup Bey is behind it all
They're going to kill me.
Well Yakup Bey..
-Turan
-Konur Bey
Germiyanid Mehmet has surrounded Yenisehir.
Tell the Alps to be ready.
Turan.
Tell the Alps to prepare in secret.
Don't let the people find out
As you command Konur Bey.
Osman Bey is with Remus, Konur Bey.
Thank you Dark All.
My Bey!
My Beyl
Well you are going to give us
a big stall in this market right.
...my Sultan?
Not just you Karesi Bey.
All the Beys on this table...
...will have the biggest stalls.
But the size of your stalls..
...will be determined by..
...the number of alps
you bring to the conquests.
Osman Bey.
You invited all these Beys here.
And now you're holding a sword.
This is either intimidation.
Or it means there will be blood.
There will be.
A lot of blood will be shed.
Osman... Osman...
If you do something to my Bey.
I'll destroy
you with your city!
Yakup Bey
During your rule as the Sultan...
...you said that
there won't be an enslaved Bey.
...right?
Then tell the beys too.
Let them hear too.
Will your reign...
...include setting Beys up?
Will it include...
...attacking Beys due to your greed?
Will your sense of justice..
...become corrupted...
for power and might?
Your words will decide on...
...whose blood is about to be spilled.
Contact us for any inquiries: turkision@gmail.com